{
  "LevelId": 18,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 177,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "TAJMEHAL",
      "question": "Iconic white marble mausoleum in India"
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PRODUCER",
      "question": "Individual or entity involved in the creation or management of artistic or media content"
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "MOUNTAIN",
      "question": "Large landform rising prominently above its surroundings"
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "PORTRAIT",
      "question": "Artistic representation of a person's face"
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "TANGIBAL",
      "question": "erceptible by touch or physical presence"
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "GUARDIAN",
      "question": "Person responsible for protecting and caring for someone or something"
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BIOLOGIC",
      "question": "Pertaining to living organisms or biological processes"
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ACTIVITY",
      "question": "Physical or mental action or involvement"
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "AIRSPACE",
      "question": "The portion of the atmosphere above a particular area, often controlled for air traffic"
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "BIRTHDAY",
      "question": "Annual celebration of one's birth"
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "JOURNALIST",
      "question": "Person engaged in reporting news or conducting interviews for the media"
    }
  ]
}